

ABONGILE MAVUMA

Customer Service Consultant | Admin Assistant | Data Collector

Dedicated and goal-driven Admin Assistant with a year and five months of experience in the Healthcare Department. Adapt to managing high volume inquiries, and boosting customer satisfaction. Ready to leverage these skills in Administration.

(+27) 67-173-2920

Northgate, Johannesburg

mavumaabonqile@qmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/abo ngile-mavuma-92599715a?trk=c ontact-info

7

#

Q

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Admin Assistant/Data Collector

Dr Ngwenya's Surgery

Port Edward, SA 08/2022 – 03/2024

- Warmly welcomed 20-30 guests per shift and assisted promptly with high end professionalism.
- Maintained an organised, clean and professional work space and waiting area.
- Submitted a daily, weekly, monthly reporting on time with a weekly verification process of over 70 clients per week.
- Assisted with processing clients medical information, inputting data of over 280 clients Information accurately and efficiently.
- Collaborated with team members to ensure efficient data management.

Data Capturer

Soka Mens Clinic

Port Shepstone, SA, 02/2022 – 07/2022

Retail Assistant

Mr Price Fashion

Shelly Beach, SA 03/2017 - 04/2018

- Accurately entered patient information into company databases.
- Collaborated as a team with Healthcare providers to ensure accurate documentation of patients visits.
- Provided administrative support to ensure smooth operations of the office by handling office equipment.
- Delivered exceptional moments and services tailored to customers, ensuring that their needs were met.
- Sustained the visual appearance of the store.
- Actively Worked collaboratively with colleagues to meet sales objectives and achieve results through clear communication and teamwork.

EDUCATION

MATRIC Completed,

Port Shepstone High School 12/2016

Fashion Design incomplete

Spero Villioti institute of fashion

Online Certifications
CRM training-Dubsado
Inbound Sales
Training-HubSpot
Social Media management
certificate - Hubspot
Academy
TEFL Certification - Teacher
Record
Google Analytics- Analytics
Academy

KEY SKILLS

- Customer Service
- Organisational Skills
- Detail-oriented
- Proficient in data entry with a keen eye for detail

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Fluent in English, Zulu and Xhosa
- Microsoft Office
- Google Spreadsheet
- Excel
- Strong communicator